{
  "round1": {
    "Mining": [
      {
        "question": "Which Planet is the only one that Has Treasure mining?",
        "answer": "Arkadia"
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can you buy the tt finder?",
        "answer": "trade terminal"
      }
    ],
    "hunting": [
      {
        "question": "Which weapon type is the EP-2 Proton?",
        "answer": "Laser Pistol"
      },
      {
        "question": "which amp is commonly dropped by the bots at orthos oilfield?",
        "answer": "B101"
      }
    ],
    "crafting": [
      {
        "question": "what items are needed to craft explosive projectiles?",
        "answer": "nanocubes"
      },
      {
        "question": "what extractor is needed to craft Arkadian Hornet hide texture?",
        "answer": "Basic leather extractor"
      }
    ],
    "history": [
      {
        "question": "who is Club Neverdie named after?",
        "answer": "neverdie"
      },
      {
        "question": "What Company created Entropia Universe?",
        "answer": "MindArk"
      }
    ],
    "beauty": [
      {
        "question": "How many paint cans or textures for max success chance?",
        "answer": "323"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is the prettiest Avatar?",
        "answer": "Jimbobbityboo"
      }
    ],
    "economy": [
      {
        "question": "What is the full name of the currency used in Entropia Universe?",
        "answer": "Project Entropia Dollar"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the default exchange rate between Project Entropia Dollars (PED) and USD?",
        "answer": "1 PED = 1 USD"
      }
    ],
    "social": [
      {
        "question": "Which feature allows players to communicate with each other in Entropia Universe?",
        "answer": "Chat"
      },
      {
        "question": "how many players can be in a team?",
        "answer": "12"
      }
    ],
    "misc": [
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the crystal palace?",
        "answer": "Crystal Palace"
      },
      {
        "question": "What planet has fishing?",
        "answer": "Next Island"
      }
    ]
  },
  "round2": {
    "Mining": [
      {
        "question": "yes or no - is sweetstuff an enmatter?",
        "answer": "yes"
      },
      {
        "question": "what item is used to enhance the depth of your mining finder",
        "answer": "depth enhancer"
      }
    ],
    "hunting": [
      {
        "question": "how much hp does a creature with 1 stamina have?",
        "answer": "10hp"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the maximum tier a weapon can reach in Entropia Universe?",
        "answer": "Tier 10"
      }
    ],
    "crafting": [
      {
        "question": "which skill do many recommend unlocking through ms repair runs before crafting?",
        "answer": "blueprint comprehension"
      },
      {
        "question": "what type of terminal do you use to craft?",
        "answer": "construction terminal"
      }
    ],
    "history": [
      {
        "question": "Which year was Entropia Universe first launched?",
        "answer": "2003"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who originally founded MindArk?",
        "answer": "Johan Leman"
      }
    ],
    "beauty": [
      {
        "question": "what color are the default male briefs?",
        "answer": "blue"
      },
      {
        "question": "which coloring tool can you aquire from next island?",
        "answer": "Elysian colorator"
      }
    ],
    "economy": [
      {
        "question": "how many ped is 100 pec worth?",
        "answer": "1"
      },
      {
        "question": "where is the unofficial trading hub on Calypso",
        "answer": "Twin Peaks"
      }
    ],
    "social": [
      {
        "question": "the abreviation of a Rookie troll whose name rhymes with duck",
        "answer": "ccr"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the default key to open the Events window?",
        "answer": "b"
      }
    ],
    "misc": [
      {
        "question": "Which is the largest planet in Entropia Universe?",
        "answer": "Calypso"
      },
      {
        "question": "what is the name of limp biscuits lead singer",
        "answer": "fred durst"
      }
    ]
  }
}